Finding Aid for the Collection of Broadside Ballads from England, Ireland, and the United States LSC.0605
UCLA Library Special Collections
- United States
  - Babylon--Black Hills, ca. 1825-1878
    - Battle Cry of Freedom The Battle Cry of Freedom. Boston, United States; Published and sold at wholesale by Horace Partridge, importer and wholesale dealer in fancy goods, toys, watches, jewelry, Yankee notions, &c., No. 27 Hanover Street, [186-]., Shelfmark: 1:2:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 19 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Battle Eve: dedicated to Edward Havey, Wilson's Zouave The battle eve: dedicated to Edward Havey, Wilson's Zouave. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, publisher, songs, ballads, toy books, papers dolls, small playing cards, motto verses, &c. 54 Chatham St., [between 1861 and 1864]., Shelfmark: 1:2:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 18 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Battle of Bull Run: dedicated to the 69th Regiment, N.Y.S.M. Battle of Bull Run: dedicated to the 69th Regiment, N.Y.S.M.. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, publisher of songs, ballads, toy books, &c. No. 54 Chatham, [1861?]., Shelfmark: 1:2:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 25 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Battle of Drainesville Setley, Henry Albert, The Battle of Drainesville. Virginia, United States; Camp Pierpoint, Va., 1861 December 31., Shelfmark: 1:2:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 28 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Battle of Willaimsburgh: Air: The Land of America Battle of Williamsburgh: Air: The Land of America. New York, Untied States; H. De Marsan, dealer in songs toy-books &c., No. 54 Chatham, [1862?]., Shelfmark: 1:2:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Battle-cry of freedom Battle-cry of freedom. New York, United States; H.J. Wehman, song publisher, 50 Chatham, [186-]., Shelfmark: 1:2:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 23 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Beautifull Nell Beautiful Nell. Philadelphia, United States; Published by Johnson, the great song publisher, No. 7 North Tenth Street, [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:2:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 20 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Beecher Scandal! The Beecher Scandal!., [United States], [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:2:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 11 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Behind the Scenes Behind the Scenes. San Francisco, United States; Published and sold wholesale and retail by Bell & Company, general publishers of songs and ballads, booksellers, stationers and periodical agents, No. 639 Kearney Street, [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:2:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 33 × 11 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Belles of the 'bus: Air: the mistletoe bough The Belles of the 'bus. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, publisher, 38 Chatham Street, [ca. 1860]., Shelfmark: 1:2:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Black ey'd Susan. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, [18--]., Shelfmark: 1:2:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Black Hills, as sung by Dick Brown The Black Hills, as sung by Dick Brown. San Francisco, United States; Published and sold wholesale and retail by Bell & Co., general publishers of songs and ballads, booksellers and stationers and periodical agents, 639 Kearney Street, [18--]., Shelfmark: 1:2:20; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 20 × 13 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Blue devils--By, ca. 1825-1878
    Printed in Boston, New York, Salem, Mass.,
    - Blue devils or the national zouaves W.H.P., Blue devils or the national zouaves. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, publisher of songs and ballads, paper dolls, toy books &c., 54 Chatham St., [ca. 1861]., Shelfmark: 1:3:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Blue violets: as sung by Charles Melville, the celebrated balladist and tenor vocalist Blue violets: as sung by Charles Melville, the celebrated balladist and tenor vocalist. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, successor to J. Andrews, publisher, dealer in songs and toy-books, papers dolls &c., 38 Chatham Street, NY, [1859 or 1860]., Shelfmark: 1:3:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bold dragoon The Bold Dragoon. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, publisher of songs and ballads, paper dolls, toy books, &c. 38 & 60 Chatham St., [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:3:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 23 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bonaparte's farewell: Air, Captain O'Kean Bonaparte's Farewell: Air, Captain O'Kean. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, Publisher. Songs, Ballads, toy books, paper dolls, small playing cards, motto verses, &c, 54 Chatham St, [between 1850 and 1860]., Shelfmark: 1:3:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 25 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bonnie blue flag The Bonnie Blue Flag. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, Publisher of Songs, ballads, toy books &c. No. 54 Chatham Street, N.Y., [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:3:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 25 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Boston tea-party Boston Tea-Party. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, Publisher of songs and ballads, papers dolls, toy books, &c. 54 Chatham St. NY, [ca. 1860]., Shelfmark: 1:3:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 25 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bounty Jumper Casten, J. Cross, The Bounty Jumper. Boston, United States; Sold wholesale by Horace Patridge, 27 Hanover Street, Boston., [ca. 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:3:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 20 × 14 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bowld soger boy Bowld Soger Boy. New York, United States; Andrews' Printer, 38 Chatham St, N.Y., Dealer in Songs, Games, Toy Books, Motto Verses, &c., Wholesale and Retail., [ca. 1861]., Shelfmark: 1:3:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 21 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bride's farewell. O, saw ye lass, with the bonnie blue een. Contentment. Major Andre's farewell. The Bride's Farewell. Boston; Middlebury, Vt., United States; Sold, by Leonard Deming, at the Sign of the Barber's Pole, No. 61, Hanover St. Boston, and at Middlebury, Vt., [ca. 1835]., Shelfmark: 1:3:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bride's farewell. O, saw ye lass, with the bonnie blue een. Contentment. Major Andre's farewell. Contentment. Boston; Middlebury, Vt., United States; Sold, by Leonard Deming, at the Sign of the Barber's Pole, No. 61, Hanover St. Boston, and at Middlebury, Vt., [ca. 1835]., Shelfmark: 1:3:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bride's farewell. O, saw ye lass, with the bonnie blue een. Contentment. Major Andre's farewell. O, Saw ye the Lass, &c.. Boston; Middlebury, Vt., United States; Sold, by Leonard Deming, at the Sign of the Barber's Pole, No. 61, Hanover St. Boston, and at Middlebury, Vt., [ca. 1835]., Shelfmark: 1:3:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bride's farewell. O, saw ye lass, with the bonnie blue een. Contentment. Major Andre's farewell. Major Andre's Farewell. Boston; Middlebury, Vt., United States; Sold, by Leonard Deming, at the Sign of the Barber's Pole, No. 61, Hanover St. Boston, and at Middlebury, Vt., [ca. 1835]., Shelfmark: 1:3:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Brigham Young, or, Perhaps she's on the railway Brigham Young, or Perhaps She's on the Railway., United States, [ca. 1870]., Shelfmark: 1:3:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 25 × 19 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Brooks's Canada song: Air--The Cork Leg--from The Evening Post Brooks's Canada Song. New York, United States; Andrews, Printer, 38 Chatham St., N.Y., Dealer in Songs, Games, Toy Book Mottos, Verses, Valentines, &c., [ca. 18??]., Shelfmark: 1:3:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Brother's fainting at the door Brother's Fainting at the Door. New York, United States; Sold at wholesale by Horace Patridge, No. 27 Hanover Street, Boston, [between 1865 and 1872]., Shelfmark: 1:3:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 18 × 11 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bruce's address to his army Bruce's Address to His Army. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:3:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bucanier's bride Bucanier's Bride. New York, United States, [1860 or 1861]., Shelfmark: 1:3:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bummers, come and meet us Bummers, Come and Meet Us. New York, United States, [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:3:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - By the margin of fair Zurich's waters By the Margin of Fair Zurich's Waters. New York, United States, [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:3:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 25 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - By the sad sea-waves By the Sad Sea-Waves. New York, United States, [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:3:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Captain Dan Rice, The Nation's Humorist, on Buchanan's Cabinet as sung in Washington City, on the occasion [sic] of the Inauguration, by Dan Rice, to over 20,000 persons, March 4th, 1857. Published by Permission. Captain Dan Rice, The Nation's Humorist, on Buchanan's Cabinet as sung in Washington City, on the occasion [sic] of the Inauguration, by Dan Rice, to over 20,000 persons, March 4th, 1857. Published by Permission.. New York, United States; Published and sold at wholesale and retail, by Joshua Peckham, dealer in clocks, watches, jewelry, fancy goods, fireworks, &c., &c., No. 187 Essex Street, Salem, Mass., [1857?]., Shelfmark: 1:3:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 34 × 14 cm. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - C:, ca. 1852-1870
    Printed in Boston, New York, Philadelphia, San Francisco
    - California's golden shield: Air--Castles in the Air Robinson, Hugh, California's Golden Shield: Air--Castles in the Air. San Francisco, United States; Published and sold wholesale and retail by Wm. Cohen, San Francisco News Company, No. 912 Kearny Street, San Francisco. (Calhoun, Cheap Printer, 540 Market St.), [187-?]., Shelfmark: 1:4:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 28 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Call me not back from the echoless shore, in reply to "Rock me to sleep" Sawyer, Charles C. (Charles Carroll), b. 1833, Call Me Not Back from the Echoless Shore, In Reply to "Rock Me to Sleep". New York, United States; Published by Chas. Magnus, 12 Frankfort St., NY, [186-?]., Shelfmark: 1:4:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (chiefly col.); 21 × 13 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Captain with his whiskers The Captain with His Whiskers. Boston, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:4:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 19 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Capture of Jeff. Davis: Say, does he fancy he does see that horrible 'sour apple tree?' DeWolfe, The Capture of Jeff. Davis: Say, does he fancy he does see that horrible 'sour apple tree?'., [United States], [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:4:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 29 × 11 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Carry the news to Mary Howard, Charley, Carry the News to Mary. New York, United States; H. De Marsan, publisher of songs, ballads, valentines, juvenile, toy-books, motto-verses: stationery, playing-cards, A B C Cards, &c. 60 Chatham Street, New York, [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:4:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Celebrated black shaker song The Celebrated Black Shake Song. Philadelphia, United States; Harris, Printer, S.E. Cor. 4th & Vine, Phila., [between 1852 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 1:4:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 20 × 10 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Charming Jane Louisa Charming Jane Louisa. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:4:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cheer for the Pilots Cheer for the Pilots. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1864]., Shelfmark: 1:4:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (chiefly col.); 26 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Christmas Carol Christmas Carol. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:4:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (chiefly col.); 25 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Clime beneath whose genial sun: Air--Scots Wha Hae wi' Wallace bled National Song: Clime Beneath Whose Genial Sun / Air--Scots Wha Hae wi' Wallace Bled. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:4:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (chiefly col.); 25 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Color Bearer: Tune--Marching along The Color Bearer: Tune--Marching along. Boston, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:4:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 21 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Come Back to Erin Come Back to Erin. San Francisco, United States; Purchased and sold, wholesale and retail, by Bell and Company, general publishers of songs and ballads, booksellers, stationers and periodical agents, No. 639 Kearny Street, San Francisco, [ca. 187?]., Shelfmark: 1:4:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 11 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Come wake up my lady love Come Wake Up My Lady Love. Philadelphia, United States; J.H. Johnson, card and job printer, No. 7 North Tenth Street, Three doors above Market, Philadelphia, [between 1858 and 1876]., Shelfmark: 1:4:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 14 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Conscript how are you? Conscript How Are You?. Philadelphia, United States; Johnson, song publisher, stationer & printer, no. 7, N. Tenth St., 3 doors above Market, Phila., [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:4:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Conscript song Conscript Song. Boston, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:4:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 19 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Constitution!: National anthem written, composed and respectfully dedicated to the President and people of the United States Widdows, F., The Constitution! National anthem written, composed and respectfully dedicated to the Presdient and People of the United States. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:4:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (chiefly col.); 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Conversion of A.W. Harmon Harmon, A.W., The Conversion of A.W. Harmon., [United States], [between 1840 and 1870]., Shelfmark: 1:4:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 31 × 23 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Courage, mother, I am going Ludwing, Otto W., Courage, Mother, I am Going. Boston, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:4:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 19 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Crow family The Crow Family. New York, United States, [between 1864 and 1878]., Shelfmark: 1:4:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (chiefly col.); 25 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cruelty to Johnny! Cruelty to Johnny!. [Philadelphia], United States, [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:4:20; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 20 × 11 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cum plung gum: original song and dance by Joe Murphy, of San Francisco, Cal. Murphy, Joe, Cum Plung Gum. New York, United States, [between 1860-1870]., Shelfmark: 1:4:21; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 27 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cumberland's crew Cumberland's Crew. San Francisco, United States, [between 1862-1870]., Shelfmark: 1:4:22; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 10 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - D:, ca. 1853-1887
    Printed in Boston, New York, Philadelphia, and Sanf Francisco
    - Day when you'll forget me The day when you'll forget me. San Francisco, United States, [ca. 1877]., Shelfmark: 1:5:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 28 × 11 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Daylight is on the sea Daylight is on the sea. New York, United States, [between 1864 and 1878]., Shelfmark: 1:5:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill. (chiefly col.); 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dear mother I've gone home to die Dear mother I've gone home to die. Boston, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:5:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 20 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dear old flag Bradbury, William B., Dear old flag. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:5:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill. (chiefly col.); 25 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dear old flag Dear old flag. Boston, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:5:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 20 × 13 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dearest spot on earth to me is home sweet home. Welcome, welcome home. Thomas, J. R. (John Rogers), 1830-1896, Welcome, welcome home.. New York, United States, [1861?]., Shelfmark: 1:5:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill. (chiefly col.); 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dearest spot on earth to me is home sweet home. Welcome, welcome home. The dearest spot on earth to me is home sweet home. New York, United States, [1861?]., Shelfmark: 1:5:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill. (chiefly col.); 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dedicated to Co. K., 56th Reg. Mass. V. M. Dedicated to Co. K., 56th Reg. Mass. V. M.. Boston, United States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:5:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 19 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dixey's land Dixey's Land. New York, United States, 1860., Shelfmark: 1:5:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dixie's land Dixie's land. Boston, United States, [between 1856 and 1870]., Shelfmark: 1:5:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 20 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Do they miss me at home Do they miss me at home., [United States], [between 1858 and 1876]., Shelfmark: 1:5:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 23 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Do you ask me if I love you?. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:5:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Do you ask me if I love you? Do you ask me if I love you?. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:5:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Don't you go Tommy Lockwood, C. T., Don't you go Tommy. New York, United States, [186-?]., Shelfmark: 1:5:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 25 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Doony Song The Doony Song. San franscisco, United States, [1867?]., Shelfmark: 1:5:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 20 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Draft is a coming The Draft is a coming. New York, united States, [between 1861 and 1865]., Shelfmark: 1:5:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 25 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dream of Bonaparte The dream of Bonaparte. New York, United States, [186-?]., Shelfmark: 1:5:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 18 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Drover boy Drover boy. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:5:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill. (chiefly color); 25 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Drunkard's lone child Drunkard's lone child. Philadelphia, United States, [between 1877 and 1887]., Shelfmark: 1:5:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 21 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dumb scold The Dumb Scold. New York, United States, [between 1853 and 1859]., Shelfmark: 1:5:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 24 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dying Soldier The Dying Soldier. Boston, United States, [1861 and 1865?]., Shelfmark: 1:5:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 19 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - E:, ca. 1840-1887
    Printed in Boston, New York and Philadelphia
    - E pluribus unum E pluribus unum. Philadelphia, United States, [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:6:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 29 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ella Ree Ella Ree. Philadelphia, United States, [between 1868 and 1875]., Shelfmark: 1:6:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 20 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ellsworth's Avengers Hudson, A. L., Ellesworth's avengers. New York, United States, [between 1865 and 1870]., Shelfmark: 1:6:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ellsworth's Avengers Hudson, A. L., Ellsworth's Avengers. Boston, United States, [between 1865 and 1870]., Shelfmark: 1:6:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 19 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Englishman The Englishman. New York, United States, [1860 or 1861]., Shelfmark: 1:6:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill. (chiefly col.); 24 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Erin's Green Shore Erin's Green Shore. Philadelphia, United States, [between 1877 and 1887]., Shelfmark: 1:6:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 21 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Es wollt' ein madchen fruh auffteh'n Es wollt' ein madchen fruh auffteh'n. New York, United States, [186?]., Shelfmark: 1:6:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 23 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Escape of Stephens The escape of Stephens, the Fenian chief. New York, United States, 1865?]., Shelfmark: 1:6:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Evening star. Forget me not Evening star. New York, United States, [between 1840 and 1875?]., Shelfmark: 1:6:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 20 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Evening star. Forget me not Forget me not. New York, United States, [between 1840 and 1875?]., Shelfmark: 1:6:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 20 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Every bullet has its billet Every bullet has its billet., [United States], [19--]., Shelfmark: 1:6:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 22 × 14 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faded-Father, ca. 1824-1887
    - Faded flowers Faded flowers. New York, United States, [between 1858 and 1876]., Shelfmark: 1:7:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 22 × 13 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Fair Lucretia Fair Lucretia. Boston, United Atates, [between 1824 and 1829]., Shelfmark: 1:7:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 22 × 19 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Fairy dell Fairy dell. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:7:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 21 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Fanny Gray Fanny Gray. New York, United States, [185-?]., Shelfmark: 1:7:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Fare thee well Kitty dear Fare thee well Kitty dear. Philadelphia, United States, [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:7:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 23 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Farewell! Dearest maiden Farewell! Dearest maiden. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:7:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 26 × 17cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Farewell, Lilly dear Farewell, Lilly dear., [United States], [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:7:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 20 × 13 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Farewell, Lilly dear Farewell, Lilly dear. New York, United States, [between 1861 and 1867]., Shelfmark: 1:7:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.): ill.; 24 × 15 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Farmer sat in his easy chair The farmer sat in his easy chair. New York, United States, [between 1864 and 1878]., Shelfmark: 1:7:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.) :ill. (chiefly color); 25 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Farmer's boy The farmer's boy. New York, United States, [between 1877 and 1887]., Shelfmark: 1:7:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.) :ill.; 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Farmer's boy The farmer's boy. New York, United States, [between 1877 and 1887]., Shelfmark: 1:7:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.) :ill.; 21 × 12 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Father Abbey's will Father Abbey's will., [United States], [ca. 1807]., Shelfmark: 1:7:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.) :ill.; 28 × 16 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Father Macshane father Macshane. New York, Ireland, [between 1864 and 1878]., Shelfmark: 1:7:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.) :ill.; 26 × 17 cm. (Box 1, Folder 7)